120 Chapel Ave. Twin Lakes, WI 53181

(630) 935-5250

tylerandrew.greene@gmail.com

Content writer with 3 years of online writing and content creation experience. Managed and written two personal blogs on different topics while focusing on web design, topic research, and SEO. A self-starter with a proven track record of meeting and exceeding strict deadlines. A quick learner with a knack for problem solving and the ability to keep composure while under pressure.

Professional Experience

THEGREENETEAM, TWIN LAKES, WI

Content Writer, April 2020–Present

- Uses SEO and keyword research tools to determine topics best suited for ranking in search while engaging our current audience
- Pulls from university, work, and past writing experience to create canny yet readable blog posts
- Balances our two main focuses of educating and entertaining with some posts focusing on one or the other, and some posts focused on both
- Continually expanding knowledge of WordPress platform and the ins and outs of themes and applicable plugins

TWIN LAKES COUNTRY CLUB, TWIN LAKES, WI

Assistant General Manager, April 2021–Present

- Managed golf shop and responsible for maintaining positive company image with walk-in customers
- Focused heavily on writing professional and concise emails to sales reps, members, management, and employees
- Trained new and existing employees on software applications and troubleshot both hardware and software platforms

Extra Curriculars

HOPE INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY, FULLERTON, CA

SGA Communications Senator, August 2019–May 2020

- Composed written, photo, and video content for upcoming events and activities
- Worked alongside Marketing Senator to maintain brand image on social media and print platforms
- Efficiently managed time and projects to meet strict deadlines while balancing course load, part-time work, and volleyball schedule

Education

HOPE INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY, FULLERTON, CA

Bachelor of Arts (BA) Accounting

• 3.4 GPA, Phi Beta Lambda Business Club Leader, Communication Senator for Student Government Association, Teachers Assistant for Chair of College of Business and Management

Additional Skills

Knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Salesforce, Excel, Photography, Videography, and Design